There's no gimmicking around here, okay?
So, I am the one
Yeah, yeah, yeah
(Activate Saszy)
Say you know
I can see you like it
Your control on my body like a psychic
Asake baby, never see you coming, yeah
That motorcycle better keep it running
For me, eh, eh
I'm two steps ahead of you
You know that I wanna keep you close
So, I let you take control
'Cause it makes you happy
You no go gree, but still you know
Say I fit take care of you
But I want a puppet show
Just keep me happy
Your loving over, eh
Your loving over me
I want it all, ah-eh
I want it over again
Your loving over, eh
Your loving over me
I want it all, ah-eh
Come take control of me
Let's go, let's go
Speak in tongues like boy Alinko
Speaking on my Duolingo
Let's go, let's go
Ahn, I can see you like
I know what you like
I can see you like it (you like it)
Your control on my body like a psychic (a psychic)
Asake baby, never see you coming (see you coming)
That motorcycle better keep it running (it running)
For me (for me, baby)
I'm two steps ahead of you
You know that I wanna keep you close
So, I let you take control
'Cause it makes you happy
You no go gree, but still you know
Say I fit take care of you
But I want a puppet show
Just keep me happy
Niphkeys (Niphkeys)
Sugar