Hey!
♫
Yeah
When I get chills at night, I feel it deep inside
Without you, yeah (hey!)
Know how to satisfy, keepin' that tempo right
Pictures in my mind on replay
I'm gonna touch the pain away (hey!)
I know how to scream my own name
Scream my name
(I love me)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (hey)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (I love me)
Can't help myself, no, I don't need anybody else
Anytime, day or night
(I love me)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (hey)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (I love me)
Can't help myself, no, I don't need anybody else
Anytime that I like
(I love me)
I take it nice and slow, feeling good on my own
Without you, yeah (hey!)
Got me speaking in tongues, the beautiful it comes
I'm gonna put my body first
And love me so hard 'til it hurts (hey!)
I know how to scream out the words
Scream the words
(I love me)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (hey)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (I love me)
Can't help myself, no, I don't need anybody else
Anytime, day or night
(I love me)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (hey)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (I love me)
Can't help myself, no, I don't need anybody else
Anytime that I like
(I love me)
Ah, la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la ah (hey)
Ah, la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la ah (I love me)
Ah, la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la ah
Anytime that I like (I love)
♫
(Hey, yeah)
Yeah, I know how to scream my own name
Scream my name
Ooh-ooh-ooh-oh
(I love me)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (hey)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (I love me)
Can't help myself, no, I don't need anybody else
Anytime, day or night
(I love me)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (hey)
Gonna love myself, no, I don't need anybody else (don't need nobody else)
Can't help myself, no, I don't need anybody else
Anytime that I like
(I love me) (hey)
Ah, la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la ah (nobody else) (hey)
Anytime that I like
(I love me)